<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Barfwaffle]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Barfwaffle]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 09:28:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Raps]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Raps</h1><p>Once apon a time there there was a beautiful, though very prude lady. But once I saw her ankle and I could not help myself. I asked her for a date. FoIf she would accompany me on Saturday for a ride into town for some rock candy. We got a hotel and I gave her some rock candy. She insisted that she suck the candy for a while before we started to take her clothing off. That took a long time. We fell onto the bed exhausted. I was just falling asleep when I noticing that she was back at it with the rock candy. I surmise that the poor woman was much deprived of many of the good things in life. She joined me for trips into town on many following Saturdays, until her uncle caught her with the candy in her mouth, and made her leave to county to live with her stoic aunt. No problem for me though. I figured that the old lady needed a good taste of the sweet rock candy. As suspected within an hour she was gobbling candy stick like there was no tomorrow. Within 2 days my girl and her aunt were sharing their new confections. One would start with the 2 jawbreakers, and the other with the rock candy. They had a nack of knowing exactly when to transition over to the alternate sweet, until they could feel the the grand prize they were waiting for was about to make it's way out of the chamber and into the world, where they shared it like rare honey.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/92b5e9ad6b257b0ed91446fb0e7ba3c30a6bdd2b.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>undefinedraps/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">687467bd-10bf-480f-9093-3ecf34dd2f4e</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 09:28:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>